MELE Console Enabler

For: ME1, ME2, ME3 - Last game version tested: 48602 (June 7th, 2021)

This plugin enables the Unreal Engine 3 console and can be used with any of the three games.

The scheme used to enable the console is the same for all three games now, the only difference is where changes must be made - the algorithm now calculates this by itself, so chances are this method may work with future game updates easily.